DAN SON THANH

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

Software engineer with 3+ years of strong experience in Front-end Development, Back-end Development areas with a willingness to learn new technology. Knowledgeable in user interface and debugging processes. Bringing forth expertise in design, implementation function, and maintenance of web systems. Have been working with the Scrum process. Have experience working in the product company.

Phone: 0962010214
Email: danst.hcm@gmail.com
LinkedIn: imdanst
DOB: 25/10/1995

KEY SKILLS

Front End

- VueJS, Vuex, Bootstrap
- Webpack, Lodash, Babel
- jQuery, ES6/ES2015, JavaScript
- HTML, CSS, SCSS, JSON, ,Blade/Smarty

Databases

- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

Back End

- Python, Django, Django REST framework
- PHP, MVC, Laravel, Lumen, Cscart CMS
- Nodejs, RESTful, JSON, AJAX

DevOps

- Git CLI, Github, GitLab, Vagrant
- Linux CLI, Bash script

SDLC

- Scrum, Jira
- Domain Driven Design
- Clean code
- OOP, SOLID principles

WORK EXPERIENCES

Fullstack Developer

Dynastras Vietnam

Aug 2020 – Present

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

- Responsibilities:
 - Maintenance of web systems and coding fix bugs.
 - Developing internal API based on Django-rest-framework.
 - o Developing new features based on the Django framework.
 - Coding frontend web using Vue.js.
 - Developing, design and implementation of the new API endpoints as a part of a single page application.
 - Resolve technical problems relating to the business customers resulting in system performance.
- Technologies used :
 - Python, Postgresql, Javascript, Scss.
- Framework / Library used :
 - Django, Django REST framework, Vue.js, jQuery.
- Editor / Tools used :

PyCharm, Visual Studio Code (VSCode), Postman, DBeaver.

PHP Web Developer

Oct 2019 – Aug 2020 Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

Hybrid Technologies Co., Ltd. (Evolable Asia Co., Ltd)

- Responsibilities:
 - Maintenance web system and coding fix bugs.
 - Developing internal API use for Frontend (API base on laravel).
 - Coding change style UI web
- Technologies used :
 - o PHP, MySQL, Javascript.
- Framework / Library used :
 - o Laravel (based on Domain Driven Design pattern), jQuery, Sass.
- Editor / Tools used:
 - o PHPStorm, Visual Studio Code (VSCode), Postman, HeidiSQL.

0

PHP Web Developer

Jan 2018 - Oct 2019

Nguyen Kim Trading Joint Stock Company

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

- Responsibilities:
 - Maintenance web system and fixbug.
 - o Developing module CMS Nguyen Kim.
 - Implement online payment gateway VnPay.
 - o Implement delivery API of Giao Hang Nhanh partner.
 - Development API use for web frontend (Restful API base on laravel lumen, API base on NodeJS).
- Technologies used :
 - PHP, MySQL, Javascript.
- Framework / Library used :
 - o Cscart CMS, Laravel Lumen, jQuery, Webpack, Sass.
- Editor / Tools used :
 - PHPStorm, Visual Studio Code (VSCode), Postman, HeidiSQL.

EDUCATION

• Can Tho University, Can Tho, 2013 -2017. Engineering Diploma in Information Technology.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- English language: good communication.
- Personal hobbies: running, cycling, horror movies.